Catherwood Library Collected Labor Publications 6384 PUBS
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Catherwood Library Collected Labor Publications
1890-1998
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
MartinP. Catherwood Library
6384 PUBS
29 cubic feet
29 linear ft.
Publications.
Collection consists of publication donated to Catherwood Library which the library subsequently donated to the Kheel Center. It is a mix of union, company, government, and NGO publications.
8491138
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, May 22, 2014
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, March 08, 2016
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 5583/1: Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 1 5583/2: Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 2 5583/4: Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 4. Corporate and Organizational Publications 5583/5: Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 5 5583/6: Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 6 6046: Archives Union File (AUF)
Martin P. Catherwood Library
8491138
- A-C View, 1949-1950 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- A-C View, 1951-1952 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- A-C View, 1955-1956 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- A-C View, 1957-1958 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- A-C View, 1959-1960 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- A-C View, 1961-1962 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- A-C View, 1963-1964 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- 27 Questions and Answers On The Open Shop Movement (Box 1, Folder 8)
  Scope and Contents
  ACWA
- ACWA on Trial, 1926 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- The Advance, 1931 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Amalgamated Illustrated Almanac, 1923 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Amalgamated Illustrated Almanac, 1924 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Be On Your Guard (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Bibliography, 1924 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Board of Arbitration, 1921 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Bread and Roses, 1934 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Cincinnati Joint Board, 1928-1938 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- The Constitution of the United States (Box 1, Folder 18)
  Compliments of ACWA
- Convention Programs, 1940-1954 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Did You Get Your Share? (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Don't Let Your Dollars Scab (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Five Decades of Organized Labor, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Get On The Bandwagon (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Industrial Conflicts: Strikes (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Labor in the United States, 1929 (Box 1, Folder 25)
- The Law Gives You the Right to Collective Bargaining (Box 1, Folder 26)
- Leo Wolman, 1923 (Box 1, Folder 27)
- A Manual for Trade Union Speakers, 1936 (Box 1, Folder 28)
- Now It Can Be Done (Box 1, Folder 29)
- Readings for May First and Thoughts for May Second, 1923 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- The Reasons Why You Should Join ACWA (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Recent Developments in Trade Unionism, 1921 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- The Rise of the Clothing Workers, 1921 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Rochester (NY) Joint Board, 1939 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Sewer Journalism in a Slick Magazine, 1940 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- South Jersey Joint Board, 1938 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Strikes Under the New Deal (Box 2, Folder 8)
- These Twenty Years, 1934 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- To Promote General Welfare, 1950 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Unemployment Insurance Fund, 1923 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Unemployment Insurance Fund, 1928 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Union Builder, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- UNITE and Fight, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  UNITE
- The Welfare Program of the ACWA, 1954 (Box 2, Folder 15)
- Where Workers Rule, 1922 (Box 2, Folder 16)
- ATAE News, 1949-1951 (Box 2, Folder 18)
- ATAE News and ASAE News, 1952-1956 (Box 2, Folder 19)
- ASAE News, 1957-1962 (Box 2, Folder 20)
- Accident Prevention Information, 1938-1944 (Box 2, Folder 21)
- Accident Prevention Information, 1945-1954 (Box 2, Folder 22)
- Accident Prevention Information for Marketers, 1940-1954 (Box 2, Folder 23)
- Acme Reporter, 1950-1961 (Box 2, Folder 24)
- Agriculture (Box 2, Folder 25)
- Agriculture (Box 2, Folder 26)
- Agriculture (Box 2, Folder 27)
- Agriculture (Box 2, Folder 28)
- American Labor Yearbook, 1916 (Box 2, Folder 29)
- American Labor Yearbook, 1919-1920 (Box 2, Folder 30)
- American Labor Yearbook, 1921-1922 (Box 2, Folder 31)
- American Labor Yearbook, 1923-1924 (Box 2, Folder 32)
- American Labor Yearbook, 1925 (Box 2, Folder 33)
- American Labor Yearbook, 1926 (Box 2, Folder 34)
- American Labor Yearbook, 1927 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- American Labor Yearbook, 1929 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- American Labor Yearbook, 1930 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- American Labor Yearbook, 1931 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- American Labor Yearbook, 1932 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Botanist, 1946-1947 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Botanist, 1948 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Botanist, 1949 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Botanist, 1950 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Botanist, 1951 (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Botanist, 1952-1957 (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Building Trades Information Bulletin, 1951-1957 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Building Trades Information Bulletin, 1958-1969 (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Building Trades Information Bulletin, 1970-1972 (Box 3, Folder 14)
- Building Trades News in Brief, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 15)
- Building Trades Report (Box 3, Folder 16)
- Building Trades Report of Meeting, 1952 (Box 3, Folder 17)
- Bureau of Labor Statistics, 1905-1906 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Bureau of Labor Statistics, 1907-1908 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Bureau of Labor Statistics, 1911-1912 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- C&0 RR, 1926 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- C&0 RR, 1927 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- C&0 RR, 1927 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- C&0 RR, 1927 (Box 4, Folder 7)
- C&0 RR, 1928 (Box 4, Folder 8)
- C&0 RR, 1928 (Box 4, Folder 9)
- CIO, 1936 (Box 4, Folder 10)
- CIO, 1937-1939 (Box 4, Folder 11)
- Chemical Workers Information Bulletin, 1967 (Box 4, Folder 12)
- Chemical Workers Information Bulletin, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 13)
- Chemical Workers Information Bulletin, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 14)
- Chemical Workers Information Bulletin, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 15)
- Chemical Workers Information Bulletin, 1970 (Box 4, Folder 16)
- Chemical Workers Information Bulletin, 1970 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  French
- Chemical Workers Information Bulletin, 1971-1972 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Chemical Workers Information Bulletin, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Chemical Workers Bulletin, 1965-1967 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Chemical Workers Information, 1964 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Chemical Workers Information, 1965 (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Chemical Workers Information, 1966 (Box 5, Folder 6)
- Chemical Workers Information, 1968-1969 (Box 5, Folder 7)
- Chemical Workers Information, 1970-1973 (Box 5, Folder 8)
- Circle News, 1943-1944 (Box 5, Folder 9)
- Circle News, 1944 (Box 5, Folder 10)
- Circle News, 1945 (Box 5, Folder 11)
- Circle News, 1945 (Box 5, Folder 12)
- Circle News, 1946 (Box 5, Folder 13)
- Circle News, 1946 (Box 5, Folder 14)
- Circle News, 1947 (Box 5, Folder 15)
- Circle News, 1947 (Box 5, Folder 16)
- Circle News, 1948 (Box 5, Folder 17)
- Circle News, 1948 (Box 5, Folder 18)
- Circle News, 1949 (Box 5, Folder 19)
- Circle News, 1949 (Box 5, Folder 20)
- Circle News, 1950 (Box 5, Folder 21)
- Circle News, 1950 (Box 5, Folder 22)
- Circle News, 1951 (Box 5, Folder 23)
- Circle News, 1951 (Box 5, Folder 24)
- Circle News, 1952 (Box 6, Folder 1)
- Circle News, 1952 (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Circle News, 1953 (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Circle News, 1953 (Box 6, Folder 4)
- Circle News, 1954 (Box 6, Folder 5)
- Circle News, 1954 (Box 6, Folder 6)
- Circle News, 1955 (Box 6, Folder 7)
- Circle News, 1956 (Box 6, Folder 8)
- Circle News, 1956 (Box 6, Folder 9)
- Circle News, 1957 (Box 6, Folder 10)
- Circle News, 1957 (Box 6, Folder 11)
- Circle News, 1958 (Box 6, Folder 12)
- Circle News, 1958 (Box 6, Folder 13)
- Circle News, 1959 (Box 6, Folder 14)
- Circle News, 1959 (Box 6, Folder 15)
- Clothing Industry, 1987-1988 (Box 6, Folder 16)
- Clothing Workers, 1951-1952 (Box 6, Folder 17)
- Cooperation, 1940 (Box 6, Folder 18)
- Cooperation, 1941 (Box 6, Folder 19)
- Cooperation, 1942 (Box 6, Folder 20)
- Cooperation, 1943 (Box 6, Folder 21)
- Cooperation, 1944 (Box 6, Folder 22)
- Cooperation, 1945 (Box 6, Folder 23)
- Cooperation, 1946 (Box 6, Folder 24)
- Cooperation, 1947 (Box 7, Folder 1)
- Cooperation, 1948 (Box 7, Folder 2)
- Cooperation, 1949 (Box 7, Folder 3)
- Cooperation, 1950 (Box 7, Folder 4)
- Cooperation, 1951 (Box 7, Folder 5)
- Cooperation, 1952 (Box 7, Folder 6)
- Cooperation, 1953 (Box 7, Folder 7)
- Cooperation, 1954 (Box 7, Folder 8)
- Cooperation, 1955 (Box 7, Folder 9)
- Cooperation, 1956 (Box 7, Folder 10)
- Cooperation, 1957 (Box 7, Folder 11)
- Cooperation, 1958 (Box 7, Folder 12)
- Cooperation, 1959 (Box 7, Folder 13)
- Cooperation, 1960-1961 (Box 7, Folder 14)
- Cooperation, 1962-1963 (Box 7, Folder 15)
- Cooperation, 1964-1966 (Box 7, Folder 16)
- Cooperation, 1967-1969 (Box 7, Folder 17)
- Cooperation, 1970-1972 (Box 7, Folder 18)
- Economic Security Bulletin, 1941-1942 (Box 8, Folder 1)
- The Edisonian, 1947 (Box 8, Folder 2)
- The Edisonian, 1948 (Box 8, Folder 3)
- The Edisonian, 1949 (Box 8, Folder 4)
- The Edisonian, 1950 (Box 8, Folder 5)
- Edison News, 1940 (Box 8, Folder 6)
- Edison News, 1941 (Box 8, Folder 7)
- Edison News, 1942 (Box 8, Folder 8)
- Edison News, 1943 (Box 8, Folder 9)
- Edison News, 1944 (Box 8, Folder 10)
- Edison News, 1945 (Box 8, Folder 11)
- Edison News, 1946 (Box 8, Folder 12)
- Edison News, 1947 (Box 8, Folder 13)
- Edison News, 1948 (Box 8, Folder 14)
- Edison News, 1949 (Box 8, Folder 15)
- Edison News, 1950 (Box 8, Folder 16)
- Edison News, 1951 (Box 8, Folder 17)
- Edison News, 1952 (Box 8, Folder 18)
- Edison News, 1953 (Box 8, Folder 19)
- Edison News, 1954 (Box 8, Folder 20)
- Edison News, 1955 (Box 8, Folder 21)
- Edison News, 1956 (Box 8, Folder 22)
- Edison News, 1957 (Box 9, Folder 1)
- Edison News, 1958 (Box 9, Folder 2)
- Edison News, 1959 (Box 9, Folder 3)
- Edison News, 1960 (Box 9, Folder 4)
- Edison News, 1961 (Box 9, Folder 5)
- Edison News, 1962 (Box 9, Folder 6)
- Edison News, 1963 (Box 9, Folder 7)
- Edison News, 1964 (Box 9, Folder 8)
- Edison News, 1965 (Box 9, Folder 9)
- Edison News, 1966 (Box 9, Folder 10)
- Edison News, 1967 (Box 9, Folder 11)
- Edison News, 1968 (Box 9, Folder 12)
- Edison News, 1969 (Box 9, Folder 13)
- Edison News, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 14)
- Edison News, 1971 (Box 9, Folder 15)
- Edison News, 1972 (Box 9, Folder 16)
- Edison News, 1973 (Box 9, Folder 17)
- Edison News, 1974 (Box 9, Folder 18)
- Edison News, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 19)
- Edison News and Edison Life, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 20)
- Edison Life, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 21)
- Boston Edison Company, 1952 (Box 9, Folder 22)
- Erie RR, 1911 (Box 10, Folder 1)
- Erie RR, 1912 (Box 10, Folder 2)
- Erie RR, 1912 (Box 10, Folder 3)
- Erie RR, 1913 (Box 10, Folder 4)
- Erie RR, 1913 (Box 10, Folder 5)
- Erie RR, 1914 (Box 10, Folder 6)
- Erie RR, 1914 (Box 10, Folder 7)
- Erie RR, 1915 (Box 10, Folder 8)
- Erie RR, 1915 (Box 10, Folder 9)
- Erie RR, 1925 (Box 10, Folder 10)
- Erie RR, 1926 (Box 10, Folder 11)
- Erie RR, 1926 (Box 10, Folder 12)
- Erie RR, 1927 (Box 10, Folder 13)
- Erie RR, 1927 (Box 10, Folder 14)
- Food, Tobacco and Beverage Industries Bulletin, 1950-1958 (Box 10, Folder 15)
- Food, Tobacco and Beverage Industries Bulletin, 1959-1960 (Box 10, Folder 16)
- Food, Tobacco and Beverage Industries Bulletin, 1961 (Box 10, Folder 17)
- Food, Tobacco and Beverage Industries News Bulletin, 1962 (Box 10, Folder 18)
- Food, Tobacco and Beverage Industries News Bulletin, 1963 (Box 10, Folder 19)
- Food, Tobacco and Beverage Industries News Bulletin, 1964 (Box 10, Folder 20)
- Food, Tobacco and Beverage Industries News Bulletin, 1967-1968 (Box 11, Folder 1)
- Food, Tobacco and Beverage Industries News Bulletin, 1969-1970 (Box 11, Folder 2)
- Food, Tobacco and Beverage Industries Bulletin, 1971 (Box 11, Folder 3)
- Food, Tobacco and Beverage Industries Bulletin, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 4)
- American Expansion: A Book of Maps, 1962 (Box 11, Folder 5)
- Annual Holidays With Pay: A World Survey of National Law and Practice, 1964 (Box 11, Folder 6)
- Do You Know Labor, 1940 (Box 11, Folder 7)
- Freedom of Association: A Workers' Education Manual, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 8)
- Lichenstein's Fictions, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 9)
- This Generation Has A Rendezvous With Destiny (Box 11, Folder 10)
- The Truth (Box 11, Folder 11)
- Highlights, 1946-1966 (Box 11, Folder 12)
- Highlights, 1967-1975 (Box 11, Folder 13)
- Reports of the Immigration Commission, 1911 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  Vol.11
- Reports of the Immigration Commission, 1911 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  Vol.13
- Reports of the Immigration Commission, 1911 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  Vol.14
- Reports of the Immigration Commission, 1911 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  Vol.17
- Reports of the Immigration Commission, 1911 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  Vol.18
- Reports of the Immigration Commission, 1911 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  Vol.19
- Reports of the Immigration Commission, 1911 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  Vol.20
- Industrial and Labor Relations Report, 1974 (Box 12, Folder 2)
- Industrial Relations, 1944-1946 (Box 12, Folder 3)
- Industrial Relations, 1946-1947 (Box 12, Folder 4)
- Industrial Relations, 1947-1948 (Box 12, Folder 5)
- Industrial Relations, 1948 (Box 12, Folder 6)
- International Federation of Journalists Direct Line, 1964-1967 (Box 12, Folder 7)
- LOF Glass, 1946-1950 (Box 12, Folder 8)
- LOF Glass, 1951-1953 (Box 12, Folder 9)
- LOF Glass, 1954-1956 (Box 12, Folder 10)
- LOF Glass, 1957-1961 (Box 12, Folder 11)
- Land and Work, 1958 (Box 12, Folder 12)
- Land and Work, 1959 (Box 12, Folder 13)
- Land and Labour, 1960 (Box 12, Folder 14)
- Land and Labour, 1961 (Box 12, Folder 15)
- Land and Labour, 1962 (Box 12, Folder 16)
- Land and Labour, 1963-1964 (Box 12, Folder 17)
- Land and Labour, 1965-1966 (Box 12, Folder 18)
- Land and Labour, 1967-1970 (Box 12, Folder 19)
- Leather and Footwear Industries, 1992 (Box 12, Folder 20)
- Leather Workers, 1967-1970 (Box 12, Folder 21)
- Life Insurance Reveille, 1946-1949 (Box 13, Folder 1)
- Life Insurance Reveille, 1950-1953 (Box 13, Folder 2)
- Link Belt News, 1939-1941 (Box 13, Folder 3)
- Link Belt News, 1942-1945 (Box 13, Folder 4)
- Link Belt News, 1946-1949 (Box 13, Folder 5)
- Link Belt News, 1950-1952 (Box 13, Folder 6)
- Link Belt News, 1953-1955 (Box 13, Folder 7)
- Link Belt News, 1956-1957 (Box 13, Folder 8)
- Link Belt News, 1958-1959 (Box 13, Folder 9)
- Link Belt News, 1960-1963 (Box 13, Folder 10)
- Link Belt News, 1964-1967 (Box 13, Folder 11)
- Metal Workers Information Bulletin, 1951-1952 (Box 13, Folder 12)
- Metal Workers Information Bulletin, 1954 (Box 13, Folder 13)
- Metal Workers Information Bulletin, 1955-1957 (Box 13, Folder 14)
- Metal Workers Information Bulletin, 1957-1958 (Box 13, Folder 15)
- Metal Workers Information Bulletin, 1959 (Box 13, Folder 16)
- Metal Workers Information Bulletin, 1960 (Box 13, Folder 17)
- Metal Workers Information Bulletin, 1960-1961 (Box 13, Folder 18)
- Metal Workers Information Bulletin, 1962 (Box 13, Folder 19)
- Metal Workers Bulletin, 1962-1964 (Box 13, Folder 20)
- Metal Workers Bulletin, 1965 (Box 13, Folder 21)
- Metal Workers Bulletin, 1966 (Box 13, Folder 22)
- Metal Workers Bulletin, 1967 (Box 13, Folder 23)
- Metalworkering Unions In Action, 1967-1968 (Box 14, Folder 1)
- Metalworkering Unions In Action, 1969 (Box 14, Folder 2)
- Metalworkering Unions In Action, 1970 (Box 14, Folder 3)
- Metalworkering Unions In Action, 1971 (Box 14, Folder 4)
- Metalworkering Unions In Action, 1972 (Box 14, Folder 5)
- Metalworkering Unions In Action, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 6)
- Metal Workers Circular, 1971-1973 (Box 14, Folder 7)
- 5th Metal and Engineering Conference, 1953 (Box 14, Folder 8)
- Bulletin of Metal Industries, 1967 (Box 14, Folder 9)
- The Modern Millworker, 1954-1955 (Box 14, Folder 10)
- Miners Information Bulletin, 1950-1953 (Box 14, Folder 11)
- Miners Information Bulletin, 1954 (Box 14, Folder 12)
- Miners Information Bulletin, 1955 (Box 14, Folder 13)
- Miners Information Bulletin, 1956-1959 (Box 14, Folder 14)
- Miners Information Bulletin, 1960-1963 (Box 14, Folder 15)
- Miners Information Bulletin, 1964-1968 (Box 14, Folder 16)
- Miners Information Bulletin, 1969-1970 (Box 14, Folder 17)
- Miners Information Bulletin, 1971 (Box 14, Folder 18)
- Miners Information Bulletin, 1972 (Box 14, Folder 19)
- Miners Information Bulletin, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 20)
- Monitor, 1945-1946 (Box 14, Folder 21)
- Monitor, 1960-1962 (Box 14, Folder 22)
- Monitor, 1963-1964 (Box 15, Folder 1)
- Monitor, 1965-1966 (Box 15, Folder 2)
- Monitor, 1967-1968 (Box 15, Folder 3)
- Monitor, 1969-1970 (Box 15, Folder 4)
- National Manpower Council, 1953 (Box 15, Folder 5)
- National Recovery Administration, 1936 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  Review Part A
- National Recovery Administration (Box 15, Folder 7)
  Review Session 7(a)
- New York Central Lines Magazine, 1925 (Box 15, Folder 8)
- New York Central Lines Magazine, 1926 (Box 15, Folder 9)
- New York Central Lines Magazine, 1927 (Box 15, Folder 10)
- New York Central Lines Magazine, 1927 (Box 15, Folder 11)
- New York Central Lines Magazine, 1927 (Box 15, Folder 12)
- New York Central Lines Magazine, 1928 (Box 15, Folder 13)
- New York Central Lines Magazine, 1928 (Box 15, Folder 14)
- PCC News, 1943-1945 (Box 15, Folder 15)
- PCC News, 1946 (Box 15, Folder 16)
- PCC News, 1947 (Box 15, Folder 17)
- PCC News, 1948-1950 (Box 15, Folder 18)
- PCC News, 1951-1954 (Box 15, Folder 19)
- Pequot Shield, 1938-1941 (Box 16, Folder 1)
- Pequot Shield, 1942-1944 (Box 16, Folder 2)
- Pequot Shield, 1945-1948 (Box 16, Folder 3)
- Public Employees Information Bulletin, 1957-1958 (Box 16, Folder 4)
- Public Employees Information Bulletin, 1959-1960 (Box 16, Folder 5)
- Public Employees Information Bulletin, 1960-1963 (Box 16, Folder 6)
- Public Employees Information Bulletin, 1964-1966 (Box 16, Folder 7)
- The Reading, 1937-1942 (Box 16, Folder 8)
- The Reading, 1943-1947 (Box 16, Folder 9)
- The Reading, 1948-1951 (Box 16, Folder 10)
- Rochester (NY) Chamber of Commerce Business Bulletin, 1947-1967 (Box 16, Folder 11)
- Rochester (NY) Chamber of Commerce Business Bulletin, 1968-1971 (Box 16, Folder 12)
- Rochester (NY) Chamber of Commerce Business Bulletin, 1972-1975 (Box 16, Folder 13)
- Seaman, 1976-1977 (Box 16, Folder 1)
- Seaman, 1978-1979 (Box 16, Folder 2)
- Seaman, 1980-1981 (Box 16, Folder 3)
- Seaman, 1982-1983 (Box 16, Folder 4)
- Seaman, 1984-1985 (Box 16, Folder 5)
- Seaman, 1986-1987 (Box 16, Folder 6)
- Seaman, 1988-1989 (Box 16, Folder 7)
- Seaman, 1990-1991 (Box 16, Folder 8)
- Seaman, 1992-1993 (Box 17, Folder 1)
- Sharon Steel Record, 1944-1946 (Box 17, Folder 2)
- Sharon Steel Record, 1947-1949 (Box 17, Folder 3)
- Sharon Steel Record, 1950-1952 (Box 17, Folder 4)
- Sharon Steel Record, 1953-1954 (Box 17, Folder 5)
- Sharon Steel Record, 1955-1956 (Box 17, Folder 6)
- Sharon Steel Record, 1957-1959 (Box 17, Folder 7)
- Sharon Steel Record, 1960-1961 (Box 17, Folder 8)
- Shipyard Bulletin, 1929-1934 (Box 17, Folder 9)
- Shipyard Bulletin, 1935-1940 (Box 17, Folder 10)
- Shipyard Bulletin, 1941-1944 (Box 17, Folder 11)
- Shipyard Bulletin, 1945 (Box 17, Folder 12)
- Shipyard Bulletin, 1946 (Box 17, Folder 13)
- Shipyard Bulletin, 1947 (Box 17, Folder 14)
- Shipyard Bulletin, 1948 (Box 17, Folder 15)
- Shipyard Bulletin, 1949 (Box 17, Folder 16)
- Shipyard Bulletin, 1950 (Box 17, Folder 17)
- Shipyard Bulletin, 1951 (Box 17, Folder 18)
- Shipyard Bulletin, 1952 (Box 17, Folder 19)
- Shipyard Bulletin, 1953 (Box 18, Folder 1)
- Shipyard Bulletin, 1954 (Box 18, Folder 2)
- Shipyard Bulletin, 1955 (Box 18, Folder 3)
- Shipyard Bulletin, 1956 (Box 18, Folder 4)
- Shipyard Bulletin, 1957 (Box 18, Folder 5)
- Shipyard Bulletin, 1958 (Box 18, Folder 6)
- Shipyard Bulletin, 1959 (Box 18, Folder 7)
- Shipyard Bulletin, 1960 (Box 18, Folder 8)
- Shipyard Bulletin, 1961 (Box 18, Folder 9)
- Shipyard Bulletin, 1962 (Box 18, Folder 10)
- Shipyard Bulletin, 1963 (Box 18, Folder 11)
- Shipyard Bulletin, 1964 (Box 18, Folder 12)
- Shipyard Bulletin, 1965 (Box 18, Folder 13)
- Shipyard Bulletin, 1966 (Box 18, Folder 14)
- Shipyard Bulletin, 1967-1968 (Box 18, Folder 15)
- Teachers Unions, 1968 (Box 18, Folder 16)
- Telegraph News, 1945 (Box 19, Folder 1)
- Telegraph News, 1946 (Box 19, Folder 2)
- Telegraph News, 1947 (Box 19, Folder 3)
- Telegraph News, 1948 (Box 19, Folder 4)
- Telegraph News, 1949 (Box 19, Folder 5)
- Telegraph News, 1950 (Box 19, Folder 6)
- Telegraph News, 1951 (Box 19, Folder 7)
- Telegraph News, 1952 (Box 19, Folder 8)
- Telegraph News, 1953 (Box 19, Folder 9)
- Telegraph News, 1954 (Box 19, Folder 10)
- Telegraph News, 1955 (Box 19, Folder 11)
- Telegraph News, 1956 (Box 20, Folder 1)
- Telegraph News, 1957 (Box 20, Folder 2)
- Telegraph News, 1958 (Box 20, Folder 3)
- Telegraph News, 1959 (Box 20, Folder 4)
- Telegraph News, 1960 (Box 20, Folder 5)
- Telegraph News, 1961 (Box 20, Folder 6)
- Telegraph News, 1962 (Box 20, Folder 7)
- Telegraph News, 1963 (Box 20, Folder 8)
- Telegraph News, 1964 (Box 20, Folder 9)
- Telegraph News, 1965 (Box 20, Folder 10)
- Telegraph News, 1966-1967 (Box 20, Folder 11)
- Textiles Committee, 1946-1948 (Box 20, Folder 12)
- Textiles Committee, 1948-1950 (Box 20, Folder 13)
- Textiles Committee, 1950 (Box 20, Folder 14)
- Textiles Committee, 1952-1953 (Box 20, Folder 15)
- Textiles Committee, 1955 (Box 20, Folder 16)
- Textiles Committee, 1958 (Box 21, Folder 1)
- Textiles Committee, 1968 (Box 21, Folder 2)
- Textiles Committee, 1973 (Box 21, Folder 3)
- Textiles Committee, 1984 (Box 21, Folder 4)
- Textile and Clothing Workers, 1949-1951 (Box 21, Folder 5)
- Textile, Garment and Leather Workers, 1972 (Box 21, Folder 6)
- Textile, Garment and Leather Workers, 1976 (Box 21, Folder 7)
- Textile, Garment and Leather Workers, 1980 (Box 21, Folder 8)
- Textile, Garment and Leather Workers, 1988 (Box 21, Folder 9)
- Textile, Garment and Leather Workers, 1992 (Box 21, Folder 10)
- Transport, Port and Fisshery Workers, 1957 (Box 21, Folder 11)
- Transport, Port and Fisshery Workers Special Bulletin, 1953-1966 (Box 21, Folder 12)
- Transport, Port and Fisshery Workers Information Bulletin, 1953-1955 (Box 21, Folder 13)
- Transport, Port and Fisshery Workers Information Bulletin, 1956-1957 (Box 21, Folder 14)
- Transport, Port and Fisshery Workers Information Bulletin, 1958-1962 (Box 21, Folder 15)
- Transport, Port and Fisshery Workers Program of Demands, 1961 (Box 21, Folder 16)
- Transport News Bulletin, 1967-1968 (Box 21, Folder 17)
- Transport News Bulletin, 1969-1972 (Box 21, Folder 18)
- WFTU News in Brief, 1967 (Box 21, Folder 19)
- WFTU News in Brief, 1967 (Box 21, Folder 20)
- WFTU News in Brief, 1968 (Box 21, Folder 21)
- WFTU News in Brief, 1968 (Box 21, Folder 22)
- WFTU News in Brief, 1969 (Box 21, Folder 23)
- WFTU News in Brief, 1969 (Box 21, Folder 24)
- WFTU News in Brief, 1970 (Box 22, Folder 1)
- WFTU News in Brief, 1970 (Box 22, Folder 2)
- WFTU News in Brief, 1971 (Box 22, Folder 3)
- WFTU News in Brief, 1971 (Box 22, Folder 4)
- WFTU News in Brief, 1972 (Box 22, Folder 5)
- WFTU Miscellaneous, 1952 (Box 22, Folder 6)
- WFTU Press Releases, 1958 (Box 22, Folder 7)
- WFTU Press Releases, 1959 (Box 22, Folder 8)
- WFTU Press Releases, 1959 (Box 22, Folder 9)
- WFTU Press Releases, 1960 (Box 22, Folder 10)
- WFTU Press Releases, 1960 (Box 22, Folder 11)
- WFTU Press Releases, 1960 (Box 22, Folder 12)
- WFTU Press Releases, 1961 (Box 22, Folder 13)
- WFTU Press Releases, 1961 (Box 22, Folder 14)
- WFTU Press Releases, 1961 (Box 22, Folder 15)
- WFTU Press Releases, 1965 (Box 22, Folder 16)
- WFTU Press Releases, 1966 (Box 22, Folder 17)
- WFTU Press Releases, 1966 (Box 22, Folder 18)
- WFTU Press Releases, 1966 (Box 22, Folder 19)
- WFTU Press Releases, 1967 (Box 22, Folder 20)